import 'package:flutter/material.dart';
import 'package:qs_app/components/mcqs_content_box.dart';

class OtsMentaltestContentScreen extends StatelessWidget {
  @override
  Widget build(BuildContext context) {
    return Scaffold(
      appBar: AppBar(
        title: Text('OTS Mental Test'),
      ),
      body: SingleChildScrollView(
        child: Padding(
          padding: EdgeInsets.all(20.0),
          child: Column(
            children: [

              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Number Series Test?',
                option1: '1/216',
                option2: '2/256',
                option3: '1/206',
                option4: '1/236',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Coding & Decoding?',
                option1: '6483',
                option2: '6384',
                option3: '6438',
                option4: '6843',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'How many numbers up to 500 are divisible by 23?',
                option1: '27',
                option2: '19',
                option3: '21',
                option4: '23',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If (x – 1) is a factor Ax3 + Bx2 – 36x + 22 and 2B = 64A, find A and B?',
                option1: 'A = 4, B = 24',
                option2: 'A = 8, B = 16',
                option3: 'A = 4, B = 16',
                option4: 'A = 4, B = 12',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'In?ABC, the measure of the exterior angles at vertices A and B are 145o and 125o, respectively. Which of the following statement about?ABC above must be true?',
                option1: 'I only',
                option2: 'II only',
                option3: 'III only ',
                option4: 'All',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' Simplify: 1-[2-{5-(4-3-2)}]?',
                option1: '0',
                option2: ' 1 ',
                option3: '2',
                option4: '3',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' If p2 – 18p + 77 = 0 and 3q2 – 25q + 28 = 0, then?',
                option1: ' p > q ',
                option2: ' p < q ',
                option3: ' p? q ',
                option4: ' p? q ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' Number Series Test?',
                option1: ' 21.4 ',
                option2: ' 20.4 ',
                option3: ' 22.4 ',
                option4: ' 25.4 ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' Trade expert seated next to H?',
                option1: ' Military attache seated next to J ',
                option2: ' Trade expert seated next to I ',
                option3: ' Military attache seated next to I ',
                option4: ' Trade expert seated opposite B ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' Which of the following numbers is divisible by 4?',
                option1: ' 618703573 ',
                option2: ' 67920594 ',
                option3: ' 618703572 ',
                option4: '67920453',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: '6 2/3 % expressed as a fraction in its lowest term is?',
                option1: '1/15',
                option2: '2/15',
                option3: '3/20',
                option4: '4/30',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'How often will five bells toll together in one hour if they start together and toll at intervals of 5, 6, 8, 12, 20 seconds, respectively?',
                option1: '30',
                option2: '31',
                option3: '120',
                option4: '121',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What least number must be subtracted from 13,294 so that the remainder is exactly divisible by 97?',
                option1: '1',
                option2: '3',
                option3: '5',
                option4: '7',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Study the code given below for CIRULATED and based on the same code, draw up codes for the following words?',
                option1: 'icuxmz',
                option2: 'icufemz',
                option3: 'jcvgfna',
                option4: 'jcxna',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If the difference between the measures of the two smaller angles of a right triangle is 8o, what is the measure, in degrees, of the smallest angle?',
                option1: '42',
                option2: '43',
                option3: '44',
                option4: '49',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Nine individuals – Z, Y, X, W, V, U, T, S and R – are the only candidates, who can serve on three committees– A, B and C, and each candidate should serve on exactly one of the committees?',
                option1: 'U',
                option2: 'V',
                option3: 'Y',
                option4: 'Z',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If the side of a square is increased by 30%, its area is increased by?',
                option1: '39% ',
                option2: '49%',
                option3: '79%',
                option4: '69%',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' A train travels 225 km in 3.5 hours and 370 km in 5 hours. Find the average speed of train?',
                option1: ' 80 km/hr ',
                option2: ' 60 km/hr ',
                option3: ' 70 km/hr ',
                option4: '65 km/hr ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'How many seconds longer does it take to drive 1 mile at 40 miles per hour than at 60 miles per hour?',
                option1: '60 ',
                option2: '30 ',
                option3: '20',
                option4: '15',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Find the length of the longer diagonal of a parallelogram if the sides are 6 inches and 8 inches and the smaller angle is 60o?',
                option1: '12 ',
                option2: '14',
                option3: '16',
                option4: '18',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Find the side of the largest square slabs which can be paved on the floor of a room 5 metres 44 cm long and 3 metres 74 cm broad?',
                option1: '42 ',
                option2: '34 ',
                option3: '56 ',
                option4: '38 ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'A square of area 2 is inscribed in a circle. What is the area of the circle?',
                option1: '?/2',
                option2: '?/4',
                option3: '?/6',
                option4: '?',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'In a? ABC, if 2? A = 3? B = 6? C, then? A is equal to?',
                option1: '30o ',
                option2: '120o ',
                option3: '90o ',
                option4: '60o ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What is the measure of the angle formed by the minute and hour hands of a clock at 1:50?',
                option1: '115o ',
                option2: '95o ',
                option3: '90o ',
                option4: '105o ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),


              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The mean of 100 observations was calculated as 40. It was found later on that one of the observation was misread as 83 instead of 53. The correct mean is?',
                option1: '40.3',
                option2: '39.7',
                option3: '39',
                option4: '37',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What per cent of 2/7 is 1/35?',
                option1: '18% ',
                option2: '15% ',
                option3: '10% ',
                option4: '20% ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Study the code given below for CIRULATED and based on the same code, draw up codes for the following words?',
                option1: 'ncpxu ',
                option2: 'ncpeu ',
                option3: 'mboet ',
                option4: 'ncpfu ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The annual incomes and expenditures of man and his wife are in the ratios of 5 : 3 and 3 : 1, respectively. It they decide to save equally and find a balance of Rs. 4000 at the end of year, their incomes were?',
                option1: 'Rs. 5000, Rs. 3000 ',
                option2: 'Rs. 6000, Rs. 4000 ',
                option3: 'Rs. 3000, Rs. 2000 ',
                option4: 'Rs. 2000, Rs. 1000 ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'A’s Income is 25% more than b’s income. B’s income in terms of A’s income is?',
                option1: '96% ',
                option2: '90% ',
                option3: '80% ',
                option4: '75% ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If 1/8 of a pencil is black, 1/2 of the remaining is white and the remaining 3 1/2 cm is blue, then the total length of pencil is?',
                option1: '6 cm ',
                option2: '7 cm ',
                option3: '7.5 cm ',
                option4: '9 cm ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e', ),

            ],
          ),
        ),
      ),
    );
  }
}


